Thanks for coding along with me in this workshop.
I highly recommend that you use source control while working on your Python projects.
GitHub is a popular and free option if you want to learn more about Git.
You can check out my Git in-depth front end master's workshop.
For next steps, now that you know the basics,
just enough to get started working with APIs in Python and the request library.
I think you know just enough to see exactly how powerful Python can be
when you chain all of these concepts together.
Your next study topics are how to authenticate with APIs.
How to use the other HTTP methods like post to create resources
or put to update them and read up on me request quick start guide.
Some additional resources.
If you want to learn all about Python flask,
I recommend you read the flask mega tutorial.
It'll really tell you all about the eight disease of doing Python web development in flask.
Lastly, the Hitchhiker's Guide to Python is a free book.
I hope that today I've shown you that Python is fun.
It's easy to learn and incredibly powerful.
And I hope you continue on your Python journey.